Thank you for watching!
Ending
Nogizaka seniors and juniors clash with their pride in the second half of the gachin and three burning battles!
So far, there are almost five top contenders from the third and fourth seasons, and tonight's heated battle continues to be a series of ups and downs!
Let's see who will have the last laugh!
Let's play the next game, Mr. Himura, please!
The Person Gesture Astronomy Game
Person Gesture Astronomy Scarves
In this game, all participants tell the members about the target person using only gestures.
The number of correct answers in 3 minutes x 10 points
Correct answer! It's so big!
When I say "pass", please turn around.
Please go around.
If you pass because you don't want to do it, you get 10 points minus.
Just show me that you have the heart to do it.
Even if you don't know, if you do it, you might win.
What do you think?
I think you can see through them because they've been with us for a long time.
I can understand what they're trying to say.
I might be able to tell if they're just communicating.
That's true.
That's why I can see the others.
Please don't say you read it unintentionally or something
Come on, yes, let's go then
Let the electric bow game begin!
Mr. Moody Katsuyama.
Mr. Tamori. Mr. Tamori.
Chisato Otani
Wow!
That was fast!
What?
Oh, I'm hungry.
Um, Uma-chan?
Want some?
YouTuber?
Pose!
Aahhh!
What? Is it big?What? Is it big?
Big?
Umm!
Ohhh!
Wow! Wow!
Holy shit!
What? Who's that? Who's who? Who? Who? Who?
Who? Who?
Models
There's more.
Oh, no.
I've decided.
It's too soon.
Massa
Massa!
Come on, one minute in.
Almost got one.
That's good.
That's a big one.
Oh, my God.
It's so pretty.
It's fine.
It's pretty hard
Yo yo yo!
DJ?
What DJ?
Christmas?
Third?
Third.
Wait a minute. Sorry.
Number three.
It's hard.
3?
3?3?
Bat-o-yah.
Don't make a sound.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Oni? Oni!
Fluffy!
I don't know.
I don't know. Sorry.
What do you mean, 2 minutes elapsed?
One minute left.
Oh, shit.
I don't know.
Can you give me some more information?
Who's that?
He's cute.
Cute!
What's up, Fluffy?
Ah!
Pazoo!
Momotaro
Pazoo.
Pazoo
Mr. Kasuga
Mr. Kasuga.
That's not it.
I'm cooking.
Mr. Star.
I'm here.
That's not it.
It's harder than you think.
I can see why.
No way.
You're right.
I wonder...
No way!
Yes, I'm done.
It's difficult.That's a lot of hard passes.
That was a lot of difficult passes.
There were a lot of passes.
But it was good.
It's hard to be a YouTuber or a YouTuber or a YouTuber.
YouTubers.
YouTuber.
It's true, you have to speak up.
I don't know how to communicate.
And then Ume is quick to respond.
That's it.
I'll explain Ume.
And Himura-san...
I did the yodako, and it was quick.
That's it.
That's great.
It only took about a second.
Kusama was next.
Mr. Kusama.
Like this.
Very interesting.
Yes, it is.
Next is Nada.
Nadaru.
I've seen a lot of this.
We've all done this.
I've already done it.
If you don't know what it is, it's hard to do the nadaru
And Osamu Hayashi, right?
That's right!
That's not plum!
Now's the time, right?
On one side, like this all the time...
It's now, right?
Score for the third term.
Four correct answers, 40 points.
Surprising.
Four in three minutes.Four in three minutes.
Next is the fourth term
Can they surpass their seniors' mimicry skills?
Will they be able to surpass their seniors?
All right, let's go!
Here we go.
I know what you mean.
I don't get it at all.
I'm sure.
I know.
What is this?
Phone call.
Great.
Who is it?
Who's angry? Who's who? Who's who? Who's who?
Akiko Wada, this is Matsuko Matsuko
This is huge!
What is it?
Kash kash!
Don't make a sound!
Mushroom kash kash!
Heart-heart-heart... thank you... bye-bye...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
God, not the chess afterthought.
That's good, that's good, that's good
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
There's something awesomely stupid about that.
Cute
Good boy, Mr. Hamaguchi!
Oh, I was so angry!
I was so angry!
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
Oh!
The tennis player...
Who was that guy?
His name doesn't come up?
His name doesn't come up.I can't find his name.
Not Mr. Tetsuro.
Mr. Tetsuro.
Ruth's pass on Mr. Tetsuro.
One minute left.
And here comes the pass after pass... and the brakes come off.
Let's go for the last spurt!
Go for it!
Let's see...
Shudo!
You're fine.
Congratulations.
I'm fine.
I've seen something before.
I've seen something.
Let's see...
Like this.
I'll put my nose out.
Nose out.
Congratulations!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's it!
There's something there, isn't there?
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
There must be something.
Kumin
Kummin.
There's something, isn't there?
Pazuba
Ahhhh!
What a pity
No, there were a couple of wasteful ones.
It started with Gohiromi.
Gohiromi's something... a jacket play...
And then Mr. Nishi.
Mr. Nisan.
I don't know...I don't know...
Mr. Sadegawa was great at this.
Dari ni ni ni za
Wasn't that nice?
And you guessed Matsuko de Rakusan next, too.
That was persistent!
I watched it on TV just yesterday.
Oh!
Was that good?
It was great!
Next is Gen Hoshino!
It's a love dance, isn't it?
I'm glad we did that.
Let's do the love dance!
People who are watching... please don't be like this.
He moved a little bit.
Next, Buji Sota.
You wear glasses?
No.
They're pretty big.
I wear them at home.
You don't wear glasses.
But I won.
And the next one is a big pair of glasses.
This is an oyster.
It's an oyster.
He's a recorder microphone player.
Oh, no!
It's nothing but malice
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
And the last one is Takeshi-san.
Takeshi, you've already done a "comaneci"!
He didn't come out at all. There's a movie coming out.
You know, the one with the head?
Why did you do the neck?
I didn't understand what it meant.
It's a typical one.It's like this.
I did the "asshole" thing.
What the hell is an asshole?
It was a waste of time.
Four points, the same as the third term.
Ditto.
So that's about it.
Next is the 5th period
Will there be a big turnaround with a large number of points?
The 5th term's challenge begins
Skating Volleyball Evacuation
Volleyball... Ai, volleyball... Ballerina...
Oh, no! What?
You can't use that word.
It's only for you.
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're doing.
Pass, pass, pass, pass.
Pass, pass, pass.
Fairy.
Party Kamel
Pass!
All back
The team loses a lot of time due to a series of passes at the beginning of the game.
Can they come back from this?
Pass!
What was that?
Cute!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Great, great, great, great!
Wadena!
Ms. Hime?
Hime-san?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, shikina-san!
I see... smart!
Baseball... home run!Baseball... home run!
What the hell?
What the hell? Oh, wait! I really don't know! What is it?
Oh, man!
Oh, no!
No good gesture or unintelligible movement is conveyed by the 5th period team.
The passing hell has broken loose once again, and there are only 30 seconds left. Can miracles happen?
What was that?
That's a great answer.
Human vato prot.
Aah!
Uh-uh!
Okay, besten!
Besten!
It's a bus.
Bus.
This is Nana Ashitama.
That's right.
Yes, you're right.
Now, this is a goki, which I'm not very good at at all.
It's terrible.
First is Hanyukun.
He's skating, right?
I went skating.
I'm telling you, they found out.
And then there's Harry Potter.
I should have done a little more of this wand and stuff.
I've never seen Harry Potter.
No way.
Glasses and scratches.
That kind of information.
If I do it again, you'll have to give it to me.Osamu if the next one is me
I'm going to take out Nimura, and then I'm going to take out Osamu.
This is a common move with me.
So it's hard for me to do it alone.
I mean, there are nonstop shows.
Anyway, for a cheerful guy...
It's a good move.
I'm in.
Tetsuya Sakata, you used up a lot of time.
That's just one shot.
But the last one's a real gem.
I think your mouth is singing.
I was in the mood...
The next game is the last game.
I see.
Mr. Himura, please.
Compound Relay Time Attack.
Six players from each team
Battle the kendama
Unicycle Kendama Challenge
Relay with caster aces and
and compete for the fastest time.
How are you doing today?
I wondered if I was doing well enough to win.
That's what I'm talking about!
Maybe this is a kendama.
Can you do it?
This is tough.
Watch that part, Mr. Himura.
You can't do it, but there's a line.
Yes, I'll be strict.
If you cheat...
I'll hit you with the flag pole.
Don't worry, we won't hit you on the head.
We'll hit you on the shin.
This is how the third term members are arranged.
Can you make it to the end without making a mistake?Let's see if we can make it to the end without mistakes.
Let's go!
Clothes No. 1 Relay Time Attack!
Here we go!
We did it!
That's great!
That's what I'm talking about!
That was amazing.
Come on back here for a second.
Come on, big plate.
Come on, big plate
Big plate, big plate.
Platter, platter, platter, platter.
Easy, easy, easy.
Come on, we gotta do it fast, but be careful
I don't care how far it goes
Yumemu yumemu
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I can do it. I can do it.
Oh, no, no, no!
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
Yeah!
Go, go, go, go!
I don't care if it's the other way around.
Why is he following you, Mr. Himura?
I don't care which way you go.
Don't mind the sword ball.
A little late, isn't it?
Go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Here's a little plate.
The little one.
Whoo!
Go, go, go, go!
Back, back, back, back!
Back, back, back, back.Back, back, back.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
It's a baton, and you're not going to take it anymore.
Why is Mr. Gimla following us?
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Let's start with Ririya Ito!
I got something basic.
Let's go to the bottom
Come on, put it on, then the chair.
Slowly.
Not at all.
I'm not getting in.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on. Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
It's got a puller.
It's all there.
It's all in. It's all in.
Oh!
Yay!
It's a little bit sweet. It's a sword ball.
I've never been able to do it very well, to be honest.
The more impatient I get, the less I can do it.
I wonder what happened to the times of the 3rd year students who lost their adult time due to the kendama stop and a painful baton mistake.
This is the standard time.
I think it was fast.
And Mr. Himura followed us.
I thought I'd done it, but I didn't need that.
Next up were the 4th graders.
I'm hoping to beat my third term record to win the competition.
A persimmon on a wheelbarrow?
Yes, sir.
I can't ride.
I was in the unicycle club.
That's a great unicycle club.
Lilia Ito made a little mistake.Lilia Ito made a bit of an inadvertent mistake.
A sword ball is a baton.
Mr. Himura was very strict.
He'll bring it back.
Sehmiya is so stubborn.
I want to win.
He's so nervous, his head is full of blood.
He's so cute.
Breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe.
It's important for Semya to have a cissors!
I'm sure you're right... watching the 3rd year students, you can get some pointers on how to do it faster...
Sehmiya's really into it.
I have a feeling.
Shall we go?
Let's get ready for the Kugori relay time attack!
There's still plenty of time.
Don't worry.
I'm right there with you.
Now, now!
Close, close, close!
I can do it. I can do it.
Okay, okay.
It's a platter.
Come on, come on, come on.
If this part takes a while...
If it takes a little longer, how's that?
All right.
Oh, shit.
I got it.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go!
Quick, quick!
In the back?
Fast!
Go, go, go, go!
Oh, Ken dropped his baton.
He dropped his baton.I dropped my baton.
Here are the small plates.
Yumiki, small plate.
Nao, you can do it.
Oh, wow!
You did it!
Yay! I made a mistake.
Yay!
I tend to do that here.
It's easy to forget to hold the top ball here.
I tend to do that.
The game has become entangled, hasn't it?
And this is the anchor.
The anchor is in the butt.
On the ass.
Oh, my God.
And now the back.
Why are you looking at his face?
Goal!
That's good.
That was pretty fast, wasn't it?
Seymia made the same mistake as Lilia Ito.
Even though she left this place in the sky...
He tends to do that around here.
All I can think about is the chair.
Seimya, I regret that time loss.
I'll regret it for about three years.
I'll regret it.
And Mr. Himura's return.
No, no, no.
The miracle relay.
Who will be the anchor?
And you've always been good at kendama?
Yes.
The top of the...
I am.
I'd like to take first place.
You don't look fresh at all.Freshness hasn't shown up at all so far.
The 5th term has yet to take the lead in any competition.
Grab the victory with your fresh power!
Let's start the time attack for the 5th period!
I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Slow down! Slow down! Slow down!
That's great!
Thank you!
I can do it! I can do it!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's great.
Okay.
You did it, you did it, you did it.
OK, go.
Wow.
You're fast.
That's fast.
That was close.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Fast, fast, fast.
That's good.
Okay, now small plate, small plate.
Small plate, small plate.
Oh, my God.
Easy to forget.
I'm forgetful.
It's back... it's back...
How could I forget?
This is something human
This man forgets
And this...
Come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on, come on, come on
If we get here fast.
Sorry.Sorry.
Come on, Anchor.
Come on.
Oh, my God!
Wow, he's fast.
We're making a big turn.
It's making a big turn.
Oh, no.
You're in my way.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Run through.
Oh!
Fast.
Now the fifth season. The sword ball was smooth. I think it's good.
And why is there some kind of human flaw there?
I wonder if it's designed to start without receiving a sword ball.
I forget... right there.
Now let's announce the winner!
1 minute and 36 seconds
5th period.
And second place.
One minute and 38 seconds.
They dropped 2 seconds.
4th place
Yay!
Relay results are here.
The winner is...
The results are announced! All four events are over! The winning team in the three forest battles by machine was
Yosshi!
The second place team was from the third season, so they were upstaged in the last race!
This is the unity of the 4th season!
I'm so happy for you, Seimya!
I'm so happy for Seimya!
When Seimya lost the revenge race in the 5th, she was really depressed, right?
I mean, if you work so hard all the time and then you lose in two seconds because of my mistake...
I really can't do it anymore.I really don't want to do this anymore.
I'm not crying, I'm just saying I don't want to do this anymore.
Good luck with the anchor!
He landed a sword ball with one shot!
That was great!
But I broke it with Sala.
It doesn't matter.
I did my best, right?
I know, I know.
But the other team was up there, and I was working hard with Yumikiran.
Yumikiran was so good.
It wasn't just me. It was all the seniors and juniors.
It was like we were all working together.
That's the ending.
I'm getting into the summary.
The music video for the 33rd single "Ohitorisama Tengoku" is now on sale!
Tickets are now on sale for the streaming viewing of the Tokyo show of the national tour.
Hello everyone, I'm Mukai Tsurugi, a 3rd term student.
Lately I've been trying to invite the members out to dinner a lot,
I'm too shy to go out to eat with them.
Please give me an excuse or something to ask them out.
Please subscribe to our channel and watch us a lot.
Please subscribe to our channel.